this problem asks
us what will the code that we've been
given print
and why on lines one through
three we have a method definition for a
method called
meal on line five we're
outputting the return value of invoking
the meal method
so the question is what is the return
value of that method invocation
looking at the body of the method
definition on line
two you can see that we use the keyword
return
to return the string breakfast from the
meal method
now when return is executed it will
immediately exit the method
and return the provided value in this
case
that's the string breakfast
so we expect line five to output
breakfast
let's run the code and see what we get
and you can see that the output is
breakfast
in the case of this particular method
the return value of the meal
method would still be the string
breakfast with or without this return on
line two
and that's because
the return value of a method in ruby
is the evaluated result of the last line
executed in this case the last line
and only line executed in this method is
line two
if we run our code again without that
return
and output the return value of invoking
the
meal method you can see again
that the method still returns breakfast
you